This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Luffy escaped the war of the best with his life,
but failed to save his brother from execution.
In the days after, only thoughts of his crew could save him from despair.
It was then that the Dark King Rayleigh made an unexpected suggestion.
Let me offer you some friendly advice.
Back to our captain!
A jailbreak at the Sky Island and the incident on the Winter Island!
It's all right.
Luffy?
This is all so unexpected.
Please, Rayleigh, it's far too soon for this. Luffy?
Just my opinion, of course.
But I do think it's what you and your crew need.
Luffy's body and mind alike have suffered from this terrible ordeal.
Although there is truth in your words,
if he cannot heal, then all is meaningless.
But my crew won't know.
That's true.
They'll likely return to Saba Odi as you agreed before.
The events at Marineford were publicized all over the world.
Though you're still reported as missing, I'm sure.
Then I have to go see them.
They're waiting for me.
A promise is a promise, right?
So I need to go to Saba Odi.
Well, then I may have another suggestion for you.
Huh?
Meanwhile, on the floating island of Witheria,
the world's foremost meteorologists are busy coping with a most unruly guest.
Is it truly, truly, truly true?
That young lady tried to escape?
We're a bit high up for that.
I shall explain.
Why where are you off to, young lady?
Young baby.
Carry on.
She danced through the weather field, lickety-split.
Quite irresponsible, I must say.
Then she descended into the balloon terminal and supervised.
Sorry, coming through.
Don't try to stop me.
Then with a heavy backpack at her side,
she hijacked the balloon and took off.
However...
Whoa!
Ah!
What the heck's going on?
This thing's out of control!
Ah!
It didn't do this last time.
Did I grab a broken one?
Ow!
My balloon's going to crash!
Help!
No!
It's coming straight for us!
Oh, goodness!
We're doomed!
Hurry!
Run away!
And there you have it.
Too much excitement for me.
Hmm.
She may be a fiery young lass, but I didn't think she would do that.
Now that I know the what, it's time for us to figure out the why.
I'll give back what I borrowed!
Just let me out of this stupid bubble jail!
I've got somewhere to be, okay?
It's really important!
Come on!
It's just a misunderstanding!
Oh, wait a sec!
Horridus!
Get Horridus and he'll sort this out!
Pretty please!
We're old and you're scary!
Who knows what kind of trap you're plotting!
This is a place of law!
You'll be punished for your crimes!
Yes, what if we shocked her or drowned her a bit?
Which better befits a thief?
Ugh, you guys got it all wrong!
Please, let me out!
At least give me a trial!
No way, Missy!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey!
Oh, hello, Horridus!
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Well, well!
What a pickle!
Hey, young lady!
Hey yourself!
Another outburst!
You just weren't made to take it easy, were you?
But never fear!
You remember this fellow, right?
Here, I'll show you a trick!
Take your tightly tied wind knots like so!
Horridus, no!
I was counting on you to help me!
Get me out of here!
I'm in a rush, all right?
Are you okay?
Horridus, speak to us!
Tell us you're not dead!
Uh, yes or no?
I mean, maybe.
She hit that kind and gentle man!
What a beast!
Doctor!
Someone call the doctor!
That's most curious.
So she stole an armful of weather balls in our research notes, then tried to make a break
for it?
See for yourself.
It's all right here.
Young lady!
I'm a pirate!
What did you expect?
What's wrong with a little theft?
Gotta make a living somehow, don't I?
Simply reprehensible!
Such an awful human being!
We have a living in our ditch!
Whatever shall we do!
Just let me go!
You guys don't want me here, and I don't want to be here!
You got back everything I stole!
What does it even matter?
Would you stop flipping out for five seconds and listen to me?
I'm in a hurry here!
This is important!
Don't get too close!
She's terribly violent!
All right, I'm listening.
Let's talk.
Let's talk!
Though I should tell you, stealing a balloon was both foolish and dangerous.
You need proper training to pilot one.
You could have easily died.
Prior to this little outburst, you were perfectly eager to study here with us.
What's gotten into you?
Huh?
Read the front page.
The paper, eh?
You see that article about the pirate named Luffy?
He's the captain of our ship.
Is he?
Oh, I've seen that fellow before.
The boy's a real upstart.
Caused quite the ruckus in Marineford, they say.
He's famous for that straw hat that he wears.
Look at that grin.
He's a charming little rogue, isn't he?
Our crew has been separated for a while now,
so he doesn't even know if we're alive or dead.
I had no idea what he was going through until I read that paper.
I've been taking it easy all this time, while he was down there fighting for his life.
He saw his brother killed right before his eyes.
I didn't even know.
I couldn't do anything.
Now he's waiting for me.
And for the rest of the crew, I'm sure.
Luffy is strong, but this is too much to bear.
I want to be there for him.
I want to help him.
Hey, hey, don't cry.
You'll be okay.
Hurry up and let her out.
Oh, we're the real villains.
Look at us.
Abducting an innocent young girl and making her cry.
Give Haradoss the key.
Quickly now.
We're sorry, young lady.
Let's sort this out.
That's hot.
Where did she go?
I don't see Haradoss either.
How did she move so fast?
Thanks for everything.
Bye-bye.
Huh?
Bye-bye?
She pretended to cry to take Haradoss hostage.
And she's stealing our stuff again, too.
We can't let that little harpy escape.
Away we go.
The world below isn't ready for the genius of our research.
I know.
Take me to the sea.
Anywhere.
I can't do it by myself.
Impossible.
Make it possible.
Luffy, hang on.
Just a little bit longer.
I'm sorry.
Every time we've been in trouble, you've been there to help us.
Just this once.
I hope we can return the favor.
Help, thieves, get back here.
You've already captured me, young lady.
You don't need to pretend to cry like that anymore.
Shut up!
Aaaaaaaah!
We now return to Futureland Baltimore,
a mechanical island where the genius Dr. Vegapunk was born.
Grandpa, it's an emergency! The Freak! The Freak! The Freak! I mean the Freak! I mean the Freaky Mr. Freak! I mean, I mean Frankie!
Just calm down and tell me, kitten.
Frankie! He's acting all different, but this time it's scary! He's like some kind of monster!
Someone get me a ship!
He's coming for me!
Tell the truth, kitten. You put something strange in that poor man's stomach to see what would happen, didn't you?
Like habanero juice or kimchi soda or some nonsense.
No! Not this time!
It's an emergency, Gramps. I gotta go see my friends. I know this is sudden, but I won't take no for an answer. I need a ship, dammit! And I need it right now!
A ship? Sorry to say, but that won't be possible.
Huh? We don't have a ship. There's not a single one on the entire island. There's a liner that comes to our country each month to bring us supplies, but we don't have any seafaring vessels of our own.
Alright, fine. When's the liner due back then?
Not for a while yet, I'm afraid. It stopped by last week.
That's no good. I can't wait. There's gotta be some way around this.
You may have noticed this island is surrounded by walls of ice. For better or worse, it works like a fortress.
The only ships that can reach us are specially equipped icebreakers and certain navy vessels.
Well, this is bullcrap! I could get supplies to build a ship, but that still wouldn't be fast enough.
Please calm down. Do you want some tea or something?
Hmm. This aroma is just lovely.
Hey! I ain't got time for this! I'm telling you, I gotta blow this joint and I gotta do it fast!
My captain needs me right now. I'm lower than dirt if I let him down. Damn it all!
I didn't know.
I understand how important this is to you, but there's nothing you can do but wait.
Oh, here's an idea.
Yeah?
If I recall, Dr. Vegapunk developed an icebreaker. It should still be tucked away in his laboratory, I think.
Of course, it's been years since anyone's touched the thing. Who can say if it still works?
I know it's dangerous, so I'll stay home this time.
Then I know just where to go.
Hold on. You've gone there? Both of you without a word to me?
Yeah! And it was awesome!
What?
If it's broken, then I can fix it. I am a shipwright, after all.
That's not exactly the concern here.
I'm taking this party to the lab!
Wait! Listen to me!
Ugh, it's cold!
We have an intruder!
Someone's broken into Dr. Vegapunk's lab! What should we do?
Dammit!
Apprehend them, but don't use any firearms!
His inventions are too valuable! We can't afford to have even one damaged!
Understand?
Yes, sir!
Get back here!
Crap! It must've tightened security after the last time I broke in!
I can't get anything done with these guys chasing me!
Hold on. I get it now.
We can't shoot in here.
Don't let him get away! Go!
Wait, what do you mean the lab is full of treasure?
Vegapunk is the head of the Navy Science Division, so all of his works are valuable.
Priceless, really.
Our country's very proud of him.
Although, I suppose it's his mind that's the real treasure.
At any rate, he spent his youth working in that lab, tirelessly.
Have you noticed that mountain? A rather unnatural shape, isn't it?
I never gave it much thought. But yeah, there's a story behind it.
It's a project Vegapunk began as a child. It was meant to protect the island's people from frigid weather.
He built it by transforming the animals in the forest into a robotic workforce.
Unfortunately, it remains unfinished. It's a sort of geothermal system to heat up the whole island.
The world just can't keep up with his imagination. That's why so many of his works remain buried here in a state of half completion.
Sometimes, the technology or funds he needed didn't exist. Even though he couldn't get rid of the cold, knowing that he cared, knowing that he worked so hard, warmed our hearts at least.
That story is super depressing.
You think so?
But the people here are happy to wait for his return, whenever that may be.
Please respect our feelings and stay out of that lab. After all, it's equipped with a self-destruct button, in case you wanted to know.
But why? Not the button. I mean, why did you think I would want to know that? Like I was gonna press the dumb thing?
Either way, that sounds pretty scary. Why don't we forget about this whole mess and go home? I'll make you some nice hot tea, okay?
Sorry, kiddo. No way. I didn't come all the way out here with no pants on just to turn around. I'm getting that icebreaker if it's the last thing I do.
Don't get me wrong. I appreciate your hospitality, but I read the paper today, and it turns out that my captain has gone through hell and back.
So bye! You guys have a nice life!
I know it's tempting, but no matter what, don't press that self-destruct button!
Would you give it a rest already? Why the hell would I want to do something like that?
Hey! I saw someone down this hallway! Over there! Hurry!
I can't find the ship with them chasing me!
Hulk!
Did you hear? The Marines came by and said someone broke into the lab.
That's not good. Let's just hope they catch him.
They're probably looking to sell stuff on the black market. Even a blueprint from that place would be worth a fortune.
This way?
Well, that was a pain in the butt.
I shouldn't need to remind you, but so much as sneeze on one of Dr. Vegapunk's masterpieces and you'll spend the rest of your life in prison! I don't care if you're a Marine!
Sir!
I can't believe the doctor cooked up all this stuff when he was so young. Cause this is super brilliant work if I've ever seen it.
Half of this is so advanced it'll take another hundred years before the world is ready.
Maybe I don't want to mess with this. As a fellow engineer, I gotta respect the man's work.
Huh?
Sweet! He's got a pirate mark too?
A pirate mark too?
So, hypothetically, if by some crazy chance I press that button like you said...
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, go on.
You wouldn't, like, hold it against me, would you?
Of course we would!
News of this incident quickly spread across the world. And history would remember it as Baltimore's nightmare.
Zorro makes a wild dash to the sea as Mihawk watches on. Will the Master Swordsman impart wisdom to Zorro? Or will their reunion end in another deadly duel?
Meanwhile, Luffy begins a daring plan of his own.
On the next One Piece, encounter the Great Swordsman Mihawk! Zorro's self-willed deadly struggle! I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!